One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Wealth, fame, power...
עושר, תהילה, כוח...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates, obtained everything the world has to offer.
גולד רוג'ר, מלך הפיראטים, השיג את כל מה שהיה לעולם להציע.
What he said in his final moments drove countless souls to the seas.
מה שאמר ברגעיו האחרונים דחף אינספור נשמות להפליג באוקינוס.
You want my treasure?
רוצים את האוצר שלי?
Go ahead.
קדימה.
Find it!
מצאו אותו!
Everything is right where I left it!
הכל נמצא היכן שהשארתי אותו!
People set their sights on the Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams.
עינהם של האנשים נישאו אל הקו הגדול במרדף אחר החלומות שלהם.
The world has truly entered the Great Pirate Era!
העולם אכן נכנס לעידן הפיראטים הגדול!
Come aboard and bring along all your hopes and dreams
Come aboard and bring along all your hopes and dreams
Arittake no yume wo kaki atsume
Arittake no yume wo kaki atsume
I know together we'll find everything we're looking for Sagashi mono wo sagashi ni yuku no sa
I know together we'll find everything we're looking for Sagashi mono wo sagashi ni yuku no sa
One Piece! ONE PIECE
One Piece! ONE PIECE
Compasses? Not for me. Left them all behind Rashinban nante juutai no moto
Compasses? Not for me. Left them all behind Rashinban nante juutai no moto
I'm headed out to sea, with my heart serving as guide Netsu ni ukasare kaji wo toru no sa
I'm headed out to sea, with my heart serving as guide Netsu ni ukasare kaji wo toru no sa
Following the ancient map to the spot marked "X" reveals Hokori kabutteta takara no chizu mo
Following the ancient map to the spot marked "X" reveals Hokori kabutteta takara no chizu mo
Yeah, it's only legendary till someone proves it's real Tashikameta no nara densetsu janai!
Yeah, it's only legendary till someone proves it's real Tashikameta no nara densetsu janai!
When the world's got you down,
When the world's got you down,
Kojin teki na arashi wa dare ka no
Kojin teki na arashi wa dare ka no
lean on your crew, they'll turn it around
lean on your crew, they'll turn it around
Their biorhythm will carry you through BIORHYTHM nokkatte
Their biorhythm will carry you through BIORHYTHM nokkatte
We're gonna make the most of it Omoi sugoseba ii!
We're gonna make the most of it Omoi sugoseba ii!
Come aboard and bring along all your hopes and dreams Arittake no yume wo kaki atsume
Come aboard and bring along all your hopes and dreams Arittake no yume wo kaki atsume
I know together we'll find everything we're looking for Sagashi mono wo sagashi ni yuku no sa
I know together we'll find everything we're looking for Sagashi mono wo sagashi ni yuku no sa
Got some change to my name, POCKET no COIN
Got some change to my name, POCKET no COIN
and maybe you wanna be my friend? Soreto YOU WANNA BE MY FRIEND?
and maybe you wanna be my friend? Soreto YOU WANNA BE MY FRIEND?
We are, we are on the cruise! WE ARE, WE ARE ON THE CRUISE!
We are, we are on the cruise! WE ARE, WE ARE ON THE CRUISE!
WE ARE!
WE ARE!
Gin!
גין!
No matter how incredible he was in the past, he's just a cook now.
לא משנה כמה מופלא הוא היה, היום הוא רק טבח.
Blowing his brains out would be easy.
יהיה קל לפוצץ לו את הראש.
You want to save this man, right, Sanji?
אתה רוצה להציל אותו, נכון סאנג'י?
Then please... leave this ship without a fight.
אז בבקשה... תן לנו את הספינה הזו בלי קרב.
I don't want to kill you.
אני לא רוצה להרוג אותך.
Leave this ship?
לעזוב את הספינה?
Piss off!
לך לעזאזל!
You look ridiculous, you old fart.
אתה נראה מגוכח, נאד זקן.
What kind of example are you setting for the fighting cooks?
איזו מין דוגמה אתה נותן לשאר הטבחים?
I don't need a lecture from a little eggplant.
אני לא צריך הרצאות מחציל קטן.
Who are you calling "little eggplant," old fart?!
למי אתה קורא "חציל קטן", נאד זקן?!
Quit treating me like a kid already!
תפסיק להתייחס אלי כמו ילד!
Sanji, you son of a...
סאנגי', חתיכת...
He's not turning his back on the head chef, is he?
הוא לא מפנה את הגב לבעלים, נכון?
Gin!
גין!
Point that gun at me instead.
תכוון את הרובה הזה אלי במקום.
Are you stupid?! You're gonna die!
אתה טיפש?! אתה תמות!
I might.
אולי...
Sanji, why...?
סאנג'י, למה...?
If you're that desperate to die, I will give you a gentleman's death.
אם אתה כל כך רוצה למות, אתן לך מוות של ג'נטלמן.
But you'll need to hold still, or else we'll blow the proprietor's head off.
אבל תצטרך לעמוד במקום, אחרת נפוצץ את הראש של הבעלים.
Pristine Pearl...
מתנה של...
Present!
פנינה טהורה!
Sanji!
סאנג'י!
Why didn't you dodge that?!
למה לא התחמקת מזה?!
If I did, that damn lackey would pull the trigger.
אם הייתי מתחמק, הכפיף הזה היה סוחט את ההדק.
Why?
למה?
If you leave this restaurant, then everyone lives!
אם תעזוב את המסעדה הזו, כולם ישארו בחיים!
It's a no-brainer!
אין פה על מה לחשוב!
This restaurant is his treasure!
המסעדה הזו היא האוצר שלו!
It's my fault the old fart lost everything...
זו אשמתי שהנאד הזקן הפסיד את הכל...
His power...
הכוח שלו...
His dream...
החלום שלו...
So I've decided...
אז החלטתי...
I won't let that old fart lose anything else!
אני לא אתן לנאד הזקן להפסיד שום דבר אחר!
Sanji! Watch out!
סאנג'י! זהירות!
Pearl...
סגירת...
Close!
פנינה!
Sanji!
סאנג'י!
The All Blue?
הכחול כל?
Yeah!
כן!
It's a legendary sea.
זה ים אגדי.
It's definitely out there somewhere!
הוא בוודאות שם היכנשהו!
Because of a Dream
בגלל חלום
Don't be silly!
אל תהיה טיפש!
The Orbit A Passenger Ship
תילולסמה םיעסונ תניפס
I mean, there is a legend like that...
נכון, יש אגדה כזו...
We're seafaring cooks, after all,
אנחנו טבחי סיפון, אחרי הכל,
so we've all dreamed of that sea at one point.
אז כולנו חלמנו על הים הזה בשלב כלשהו.
Right?
נכון?
Sanji (9 Years Ago) Cook's Apprentice Passenger Ship
(9 ןב) י'גנאס דמלתמ חבט םיעסונ תניפס
I'll definitely find that sea someday!
אני בוודאות אמצא אותו מתישהו!
You say you'll find it, but...
אתה אומר שתמצא אותו, אבל...
For starters, do you even know what kind of place the All Blue is?
בתור התחלה, אתה בכלל יודע איזה מין מקום הכחול כל?
Of course I do! I'm not an idiot!
ברור שאני יודע! אני לא אידיוט!
The East Blue, West Blue, North Blue, and South Blue...
הכחול המזרחי, כחול המערבי, כחול הצפוני וכחול הדרומי...
A sea where fish from all four seas live...
ים שבו דגים מכל ארבעת האוקינוסים חיים...
That's the All Blue.
זה הכחול כל.
To seafaring cooks, it's an irresistible paradise!
לטבחי סיפון, זה גן עדן שלא ניתן לעמוד בפניו!
That's my dream!
זה החלום שלי!
That's the place!
זה המקום!
The seafood in those waters is from all over the world.
מאכלי הים מהים הזה מגוונים כמו בכל העולם!
Any cook would be itching to show their skills there!
כל טבח ישתוקק להפגין את היכולות שלו שם!
Yeah.
כן.
It's worth risking your life to look for that sea.
שווה לסכן את החיים בשביל לחפש את הים הזה.
That is, if such a sea exists...
כמובן, זה רק אם הים הזה קיים...
What?
מה?
There's no way a miracle sea like the All Blue could exist.
אין סיכוי שים פלאי כמו הכחול כל קיים.
It's obvious when you think about it.
זה ברור מאליו כשחושבים על זה.
Some daydreaming cook must have told it as a tall tale.
טבח חולמני בטח המציא את הים הזה בתור אגדה.
Now, enough with the silly stories.
ועכשיו, מספיק עם סיפורי אגדות.
Go bus the tables, Sanji.
לך לפנות כלים מהשולחנות, סאנג'י.
What a waste to leave so much food...
איזה בזבוז להשאיר כל כך הרבה אוכל...
They barely touched this one.
הם בקושי נגעו בזה.
I was sure they'd like it.
הייתי בטוח שיאהבו את זה.
Customers these days sure are spoiled.
לקוחות בתקופה הזו ממש מפונקים.
You need to stop eating the customers' leftovers.
אתם צריכים להפסיק לאכול את השאריות של הלקוחות.
Some of the food I threw out earlier looked gross.
חלק מהאוכל שזרקתי קודם נראה מגעיל.
You're still only half a cook if you say things like that.
אתה עדיין טבח חובב אם אתה מדבר ככה.
Don't forget we're seafaring cooks.
אל תשכח שאנחנו טבחי סיפון.
The sea is an unpredictable place, so it's best not to waste food.
הים הוא מקום לא צפוי, עדיף לא לבזבז אוכל.
Why don't you have some, too, huh?
אולי תנשנש איתנו קצת, הא?
I don't want it!
לא רוצה את זה!
Everyone, calm down! Please calm down!
כולם, להרגע! בבקשה להרגע!
Pirates!
פיראטים!
Pirates?!
פיראטים?!
That ship belongs to...
הספינה הזו שייכת ל...
the Cook Pirates!
פיראטים הטבחים!
It's Red Leg Zeff!
זה זף אדום הרגל!
Looks like they came back from the Grand Line!
נראה שהם חזרו מהקו הגדול!
"Red Leg" Zeff Cook Pirates
"לגרה םודא" ףז םיחבטה םיטאריפ
You're the pirate captain Red Leg Zeff I presume?
אתה קפטן זף אדום הרגל, הפיראט הידוע לשמצה?
How may I assist you?
כיצד אוכל לסייע לך?
Plunder!
זהו שוד!
Steal all their valuables!
קחו את כל יקרי הערך שלהם!
Dammit...
לעזאזל...
Dammit! I can't die here...
לעזאזל! אני לא יכול למות כאן...
These scumbags can't kill me!
הפושעים האלו לא יהרגו אותי!
Whoa!
וואה!
What's with this brat?
מה עם הפרחח הזה?
Hey, punk. It's dangerous to swing something like that around.
היי, פרחח. מסוכן לנופף בסכינים כאלו.
Look. Blood. I'm so injured.
תראה. דם. אני פצוע קשה.
Shut up! I'm not gonna be killed by bastards like you!
שתוק! אני לא אהרג בידי ממזרים כמוכם!
Sanji!
סאנג'י!
Stop it! Don't fight back!
תפסיק! אל תילחם בהם!
That kid's asking for it! Just hurry up and kill him!
הילד הזה מבקש את זה! מהרו והרגו אותו!
I don't want to die!
אני לא רוצה למות!
If I am gonna die, I'd like to take a few of you bastards out first!
אם אמות, אני אקח כמה מכם איתי קודם כל!
Sanji!
סאנג'י!
Man, you did it, Captain.
בחיי, הלכת עם זה עד הסוף, קפטן.
Always so merciless.
תמיד חסר רחמים.
I'm not gonna die...!
אני לא אמות...!
I...
אני...
Someday... I will find the All Blue!
יום אחד... אני אמצא את הכחול כל!
He said "All Blue"!
הוא אמר "כחול כל"!
That's one hell of a goal!
זה חתיכת יעד משוגע!
Captain, tell him how we couldn't even find it in the Grand Line.
קפטן, תגיד לו שלא מצאנו אותו גם בקו הגדול.
That idiot! He's still spouting that nonsense...
האידיוט! הוא עדיין מקשקש על זה...
I'm not gonna be killed by some damn pirates in a place like this!
אני לא איהרג על ידי פיראטים מקוללים במקום כזה!
Captain! Let's withdraw!
קפטן! בוא נחזור!
This storm is taking a turn for the worse!
הסופה הזו נהיית גרועה מרגע לרגע!
That decides it, men!
בסדר גמור, בחורים!
Hurry and load the treasure onto our ship!
העמיסו בזריזות את השלל אל הספינה שלנו!
We're withdrawing!
אנחנו נסוגים!
Sanji!
סאנג'י!
Captain!
קפטן!
That damn kid!
הילד המקולל!
Why'd he do that just for a little brat?!
למה הוא עשה את זה רק בשביל פרחח?!
Finally awake, little eggplant?
התעוררת סוף סוף, חציל קטן?
You're quite lucky.
אתה בר מזל.
Pirat–
פיראט-
Figures you can't move.
הנחתי שאתה לא יכול לזוז.
You think you can just shrug off a kick from me?
חושב שתוכל פשוט להתעלם מבעיטה שלי?
So the ships...?
אז הספינות...?
Who knows? The sea was very rough.
מי יודע? הים היה מאוד אכזרי.
It's likely they were completely destroyed.
סביר להניח שהן הושמדו כליל.
We're the only ones who washed up here...
אנחנו היחידים שנשטפנו הנה...
This rocky mound has neither fruits nor animals.
על הסלע הזה אין פירות או חיות.
Sure, there are fish in the sea below,
ברור, יש דגים בים למטה,
but the waves have curved the rock inwards,
אבל הגלים נגסו בסלע עם השנים,
which sadly means going down is a one-way trip.
שלצערנו זה אומר שהירידה למטה היא חד כיוונית.
All of this is your fault!
כל זה היה באשמתך!
I'll kill you!
אהרוג אותך!
Complain all you like.
תתלונן כמה שתרצה.
We have no choice but to wait for help.
אבל אין לנו ברירה מלבד להמתין כאן לחילוץ.
But if no one comes, we'll just dry up and become skeletons.
אבל אם איש לא יבוא, נתייבש ונהפוך לשלדים.
I'll become...
אהפוך...
a skeleton?
לשלד?
That bag over there is your share.
השק הזה הוא החלק שלך.
What?
מה?
It's food that luckily washed up here.
זה אוכל שבמזל נשטף הנה.
With the portions you're used to, it'll only last you five days.
אם תאכל אותו בקצב שאתה רגיל אליו, זה יספיק לחמישה ימים.
Use your head and ration your food.
תחשוב טוב טוב איך אתה מחלק את המנות.
It's a good thing we're both cooks.
זה טוב ששנינו טבחים.
Wait a second!
חכה רגע!
Is that your share?!
זה החלק שלך?!
It's at least three times bigger than mine!
הוא גדול לפחות פי שלושה משלי!
Of course it is.
בוודאי.
I'm an adult.
אני מבוגר.
My stomach is larger than yours.
הקיבה שלי גדולה משלך.
Be grateful I'm even sharing the food with you.
תגיד תודה שאני בכלל חולק את האוכל אתך.
Don't expect any pity from me.
אל תצפה לרחמים ממני.
You old fart!
נאד זקן!
You watch the other side of the sea.
אתה תשמור על הצד השני של הים.
Let me know as soon as you see a ship.
תעדכן אותי ברגע שאתה מבחין בספינה.
Until then, no contact. It's a waste of energy.
עד אז, אף מילה. זה יהיה בזבוז של אנרגיה.
Good luck.
בהצלחה.
That old fart!
הנאד הזקן!
I won't talk to him even if I see a ship.
לא אעדכן אותו גם אם אראה ספינה.
It'll be fine.
יהיה בסדר.
I have five days worth of food.
יש לי אוכל לחמישה ימים.
That's definitely enough time for a ship or two to pass by.
זה בוודאות מספיק זמן עד שספינה תעבור.
But just in case...
אבל ליתר בטחון...
I'll make it last twenty days.
אקצוב את זה שיספיק לעשרים יום.
That has to be enough time to see a passing ship.
זה מוכרח להספיק עד שספינה תעבור.
It'll be all right. I'll definitely survive.
יהיה בסדר. אני בוודאות אשרוד.
It's easy!
קלי קלות!
No ship passed by today.
אף ספינה לא עברה היום.
No problem. I'll just be patient for a few more days.
לא נורא. אחכה בסבלנות לכמה ימים נוספים.
I don't wanna die...
אני לא רוצה למות...
My last loaf of bread.
כיכר הלחם האחרונה שלי.
It's kind of moldy...
היא קצת עבשה...
What a waste to leave so much food...
איזה בזבוז להשאיר כל כך הרבה אוכל...
You need to stop eating the customers' leftovers.
אתם צריכים להפסיק לאכול את השאריות של הלקוחות.
Some of the food I threw out earlier looked gross.
חלק מהאוכל שזרקתי קודם נראה מגעיל.
Why don't you have some, too, huh?
אולי תנשנש איתנו קצת, הא?
I don't want it!
לא רוצה את זה!
My last loaf of bread...!
כיכר הלחם האחרונה שלי...
I wonder if that old fart...
מעניין אם הנאד הזקן...
kicked the bucket yet...
התפגר כבר...
He's still alive...?
הוא עדיין בחיים...?
And look at all his food!
והאוכל שלו!
He still has so much!
נשאר לו כל כך הרבה!
There's that much food!
יש כל כך הרבה אוכל!
I'll take it no matter what.
אקח אותו, לא משנה מה.
It was all his fault to begin with!
זו הייתה אשמתו מלכתחילה!
I want to live!
אני רוצה לחיות!
What are you doing over here, little eggplant?
מה אתה עושה פה, חציל קטן?
Did you see a ship or something?
ראית ספינה או משהו?
I came to steal your food.
באתי לגנוב את האוכל שלך.
If you think you can kill me, go ahead.
אם אתה חושב שתוכל להרוג אותי, רק תנסה!
I'll die of starvation anyway.
אמות מרעב בכל מקרה.
All this food to yourself...!
שומר את כל האוכל הזה...!
Weren't we going to stay out of contact with each other until we saw a ship?
לא אמרנו שכל אחד נשאר בצד שלו בשקט עד שנבחין בספינה?
Why?
למה?
This is all treasure...
כל השלל הזה...
Isn't it odd that we can't eat despite having so much money?
זה לא מוזר שאנחנו לא יכולים לאכול למרות שיש לנו כל כך הרבה כסף?
Hey...
היי...
This bag is filled with treasure...
השק הזה מלא בשלל...
What the hell?!
מה לעזאזל?!
What's going on here?!
מה קורה כאן?!
Where's your food?
איפה האוכל שלך?
You haven't eaten this whole time?!
לא אכלת כל הזמן הזה?!
Hey! Say something!
היי! תגיד משהו!
What happened to your leg?
מה קרה לרגל שלך?
And what about the food? Did you give it all to me?!
ומה לגבי האוכל? נתת לי את כולו?!
That's right.
נכון.
Without your leg, doesn't that mean your days as a pirate are over?!
בלי הרגל שלך, זה לא אומר שהימים שלך בתור פיראט נגמרו?!
That goes without saying.
מן הסתם.
Why, though?!
אבל למה?!
I never asked for your help!
לא ביקשתי טובות!
There's no reason for you to be kind to me!
אין לך שום סיבה להיות אדיב כל כך!
So why...?
אז למה...?
Why'd you do it?!
למה עשית את זה?!
Because you...
בגלל שאתה...
Because you and I share a dream.
בגלל שאתה ואני חולקים את אותו החלום.
The All Blue...
הכחול כל...
But...
אבל...
even your men said it doesn't exist.
אפילו האנשים שלך אמרו שהוא לא קיים.
But it does!
אבל הוא קיים!
When the time comes, head to the Grand Line.
כשיגיע הזמן, צא לקו הגדול.
You'll surely find the All Blue there.
בוודאות תמצא שם את הכחול כל.
As you pointed out, my pirating days are over,
כפי שציינת, ימיי כפיראט נגמרו,
so that's why it'll be you who goes and finds it.
זה למה אתה זה שתמצא אותו.
H-Hey! Geezer, don't die!
ה-היי! זקן, אל תמות!
Don't you be selfish and die on me!
אל תהיה אנוכי ותמות לי כאן!
I-I wonder...
א-אני תוהה...
I wonder how many people have died cursing the sea...
אני תוהה כמה אנשים מתו כשהם מקללים את הים...
and its grandness...
והגודל העצום שלו...
I've experienced crises like this where I was starving.
חוויתי אסונות כאלו שגוועתי ברעב.
And each time, I wished...
ובכל פעם, התפללתי...
that there was a restaurant in the middle of the sea.
שתהיה מסעדה במרכז האוקינוס.
A restaurant?
מסעדה?
Yeah. I was thinking that if I could leave this place alive,
כן. חשבתי שאם אוכל לעזוב את המקום הזה בחיים,
I'd build a restaurant and dedicate the rest of my life to it.
אקים מסעדה ואקדיש לה את שארית חיי.
Alright! I'll help you do just that!
בסדר! אני אעזור לך לעשות את זה!
So don't die!
אז אל תמות!
A weak little eggplant like you couldn't possibly help!
חציל קטן וחלש כמוך לא יכול לעזור לי!
Then I'll get stronger!
אז אתחזק!
So... don't die!
אז... אל תמות!
Hey!
היי!
Help!
הצילו!
You gotta help him!
אתם חייבים לעזור לו!
Please help the old fart!
בבקשה, תעזרו לנאד הזקן!
Hey!
היי!
The old fart...
הנאד הזקן...
gave up his leg so that I could live.
הקריב את הרגל שלו כדי שאוכל לחיות.
– What?!
– מה?!
I can't...
אני לא יכול...
I can't repay the old fart for his kindness unless I risk my life for him, too!
אני לא יכול להחזיר לנאד הזקן על הנדיבות שלו בלי שאסכן את החיים שלי עבורו!
Why are you getting up... Sanji?!
למה אתה מתרומם... סאנג'י?!
I'm getting up to keep this place a restaurant for just a moment longer.
אני מתרומם כדי להשאיר את המסעדה הזו לעוד כמה רגעים.
Does that asshole have a death wish?!
המנוול הזה רוצה למות?!
Damn brat...!
פרחח מקולל...!
You put it so elegantly for us.
זה נשמע כל כך אלגנטי.
But this restaurant is closing shop,
אבל המסעדה הזו נסגרת,
and it will henceforth be a pirate ship!
ותהפוך לספינת הפיראטים שלנו!
Stop it, you idiot!
תפסיק, אידיוט!
Keep your hands off of them!
אל תיגע בהם!
What's he about to do?
מה הוא עומד לעשות?
Gum-Gum...
גומי-גומי...
Battle Axe!
גרזן קרב!